Guide to the Leslie Cagan Papers TAM.138
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Subject Files Accessioned 1993-2014
  - Cagan article in The Progressive, "A More Coherent Movement", Nov 1990 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - National Campaign for Peace in the Middle East (NCPME): General, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - NCPME: Share Systems (Financial Arrangements), 1991 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - NCPME: Share Systems (Financial Arrangements), 1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - NCPME: Grants from Foundations, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - NCPME: Final Financial Report, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - NCPME: Fundraising, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - NCPME: Financial Records, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - NCPME: Financial Records, Nov 1990 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - NCPME: Financial Records, Dec 1990 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - NCPME: Financial Records, Jan 1991 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - NCPME: Financial Records, Feb 1991 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - NCPME: Financial Records, Mar 1991 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - NCPME: Financial Records, Apr-Aug 1991 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - NCPME: Paid Bills: General, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - NCPME: Paid Bills: Telephone, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Crossroads Magazine, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Deep Dish TV, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Domestic Partnership, 1990-1992 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Earth Day, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - After the Storm: Nicaragua Hurricane Relief Concert, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Alternative Revenue Service, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - WBAI: Finance Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - WBAI: Finance Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - WBAI: General, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - WBAI: General, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - WBAI: General, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - WBAI: Long-Range Planning, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Stonewall 25: General, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Stonewall 25: QUATT, Executive Committee, Finances, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Stonewall 25: March, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Stonewall 25: Calendar, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Stonewall 25: Demands, Basic Literature, Background, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Stonewall 25: Direct Action and Civil Disobedience, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Stonewall 25: Gay Games, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Stonewall 25: HIV/AIDS, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Stonewall 25: ILGA Conference, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Stonewall 25: International, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Stonewall 25: Media: Articles, Stories, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Stonewall 25: Media: Packets, Information, Press Releases, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Stonewall 25: Negotiations with the City, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Stonewall 25: NYC Organizing, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Stonewall 25: Other Conferences, Events, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Stonewall 25: Outreach, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Stonewall 25: Rally, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Stonewall 25: Steering Committee, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Stonewall 25: Travel, Housing, Hospitality, Merchandise, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Stonewall 25: Volunteer Recruitment, Training, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Stonewall 25: General, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Stonewall 25: Publications 1, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Stonewall 25: Publications 2, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Print Ads: General, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Resumés, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Scheduling Items, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Strategy/Planning Sessions: Notes, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Stickers, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Volunteers, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Voter Registration, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Reproductive Rights, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Dinkins Campaign: New Alliance Party, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Dinkins Campaign: "Let's Stop the Violence" Rally (May 25, 1989) (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Committee on Alternatives for the Next New York, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Petitions, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Phone Banking, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Polls/Polling, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Polling Sites/Accessibility, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Primary Day Operations, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Primary Day Operations, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Print Ads: Primary Election, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Dinkins Campaign: "The Dinkins Agenda", 1989 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Follow-up, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Information Requests, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Citizens' Committee, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Voters for a Nuclear-Free NY, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Committee for Better Child Care, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Constituency Work, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Artists, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Asian-Americans, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Caribbean People, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Disabled, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Environmentalists, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Greek-Americans, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Health Care Workers, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Housing, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Human Rights and Civil Rights Staff and Professionals for Dinkins, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Irish-Americans, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Italian-Americans, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Jews, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Labor, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Latinos, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Lawyers, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Lesbian-Gay: Primary Election, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Lesbian-Gay: General Election, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Nurses, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Peace Activists, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Religious Groups, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Seniors, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Dinkins Campaign: United African-Americans, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Women: General Election, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Literature (Pamphlets and Leaflets): General Election, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Materials Distribution, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Memos and Office Procedures, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Dinkins/Messinger Campaign Coordination, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Cuba Information Project (Cuba Information Project): Fact Sheets and Pamphlets, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Cuba Information Project: Dr. Rivas-Estany, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Cuba Information Project: Sister City Project, 1992-1996 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Cuba Information Project: Committee Minutes, 1990-1992 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Cuba Information Project: Advisory Board, 1992-1996 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Cuba Information Project: Blockade Video, 1994-1996 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Cuba Information Project: Youth Festival Travel Arrangements, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Cuba Information Project: US-Cuba Youth Exchange Participants' Evaluation and Feedback Forms; and Participants' Post-Trip Reports, Undated (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuban American National Foundation (CANF), 1992 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Cuba Information Project: Amnesty International Report on Cuba, Dec 1992 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Cuba Information Project: Anti-Cuba Materials, Leaflets, etc., 1992-1996 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Cuba Information Project: Democratic Social-Revolutionary Party of Cuba, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuban American Committee: Information and Mailings, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuban American Committee: March 21, 1992 Meeting (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Cuba Information Project: Miami Herald Cuba Poll, Dec 1994 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Cuba Information Project: July 13, 1996 Flotilla Action Alert (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Cuba Information Project: Mobile, Alabama, 1983-1995 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Cuba Information Project: Barbara Dane and Mezcla Case, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Cuba Information Project: Los Muñequitos (New York City), Aug 1994 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Cuba Information Project: Clara Suarez, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Cuba Information Project: Organization of American States (OAS) Petition: Center for Constitutional Democracy, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Cuba Information Project: Resolution to Change US Policy, 1992-1994 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Cuba Information Project: Flood Relief, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Cuba Information Project: Reports from non-Cuba Information Project Trips, 1992-1994 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Cuba Information Project: Interreligious Foundation of Community Organization (IFCO), Undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Cuba Information Project: Election Pamphlet (Spanish), Undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Cuba Information Project: Elections in Cuba, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Cuba Information Project: Sao Paolo Forum (Havana), 1993 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Cuba Information Project: Encuentro Latinoamericano y del Caribe (Meeting of the Peoples of America and the Caribbean), Jan 1994 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Cuba Information Project: V Encuentro Latinoamericano y del Caribe (Fifth Meeting of the Peoples of America and the Caribbean), 1995 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Cuba Information Project: Encuentro Documents, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Cuba Information Project: United Nations, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Cuba Information Project: Lists Used for Outreach (for Encuentro), 1990-1994 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Cuba Information Project: International Youth Festival, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Cuba Information Project: US-Cuba Youth Exchange, Summer 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Cuba Information Project: US-Cuba Youth Exchange, Summer 1996 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Cuba Information Project: Directory, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Cuba Information Project: Housing, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Cuba Information Project: Articles and Information, 1990-1993 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - National Campaign for Peace in the Middle East (NCPME): Resources, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - NCPME: Information Packet, Campaign #1, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - NCPME: Information Packet, Campaign #2, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - NCPME: Enlisted Resisters and Veterans, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - NCPME: Press Releases and Statements, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - NCPME: Articles on Gulf War, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - NCPME: Women, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - NCPME: Responses to Mailings, [1991] (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - NCPME: Organizational Structure, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Cuba Information Project: Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Cuba Information Project: Articles, 1994-1997 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Cuba Information Project: Helms-Burton Act, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Cuba Information Project: Meetings with AFSC, Oxfam and Other NGOs, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Cuba Information Project: Vitiligo Information, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Cuba Information Project: Editorials, 1991-1994 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Cuba Information Project: Advertisements, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Cuba Information Project: Correspondence, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Cuba Information Project: Articles, 1988-1996 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Cuba Information Project: Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Cuba Information Project: Meetings with AFSC, Oxfam and Other NGOs, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Cuba Information Project: Correspondence and Notes, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Social Service Workers, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Students, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Field Operations Manual, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Field: General Election, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Dinkins Campaign: General Campaign Literature: General Election, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Dinkins Campaign: General Campaign Information and Literature, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Money Items, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Samples of Literature: Primary Election, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Women, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Veterans, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Campaign: General, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Attacks on Leslie Cagan, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Primary Election: General, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Bronx, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Manhattan, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Dinkins Campaign: General, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Committee on Alternatives for the Next NY, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Direct Mail, Memos, Voter Contact, and Fund Raising, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Dinkins Campaign: August 9, 1989 Elected Officials Meeting and August 20, 1989 COBED [?] Meeting (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Endorsements, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Field: Money Items, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Field, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Dinkins Campaign: Newspaper Clippings, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Cuba Information Project: Denver, Colorado, 1991-1995 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Cuba Information Project: Connecticut, 1991-1997 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Cuba Information Project: Los Angeles, California, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Cuba Information Project: Nicaragua Anti-Imperialist Solidarity Project, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Cuba Information Project: The Cuba Advocate, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Cuba Information Project: National Network on Cuba, Jan 1995 – Aug 1995 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Cuba Information Project: National Network on Cuba: February 1995 Meeting Registration Forms (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Cuba Information Project: National Network on Cuba, Aug 1994 – Dec 1994 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Cuba Information Project: National Network on Cuba, Jan 1994 – Jul 1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Cuba Information Project: San Diego, California, 1993-1996 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Cuba Information Project: San Jose, California, Undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Cuba Information Project: San Francisco and Bay Area, California, 1991-1994 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Cuba Information Project: Santa Rosa, California, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Cuba Information Project: Tucson, Arizona, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Cuba Information Project: National Network on Cuba, Sep 1995 – Dec 1995 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Cuba Information Project: National Network on Cuba, Jan 1996 – Apr 1996 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Cuba Information Project: National Network on Cuba, Jan 1997 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Cuba Information Project: National Network on Cuba, May 1996 – Dec 1996 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Cuba Information Project: National Network on Cuba: Havana Meetings and Instituto Cubano de Amistad con los Pueblos, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - National Campaign for Peace in the Middle East (NCPME): Continuations Committee Meetings Notes, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - NCPME: Endorsements, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - NCPME: Energy Issues and the Environment, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - NCPME: Correspondence: General, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - NCPME: Date Conflict: Contact with National Rainbow Coalition, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - NCPME: December 1, 1990 Meeting in Riverside Church (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - NCPME: Endorsers and Groups Participating in Campaign, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - NCPME: Correspondence: International, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - NCPME: Greenpeace News and Greenpeace Pundit Watch (faxed newsletters), 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - NCPME: World Peace Council Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - NCPME: Institute for Policy Studies: Gulf Crisis Chronology, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - NCPME: January 13, 1991 Radio Program (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - NCPME: January 26, 1991 Demonstration: Program, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - NCPME: January 26, 1991 Demonstration: Leaflet and Poster, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - NCPME: January 26, 1991 Demonstration: Logistics, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - NCPME: January 26, 1991 Demonstration: Endorsements, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - NCPME: Labor, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - NCPME: Mailgrams: Western Union, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - NCPME: Military Families Support Network, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - NCPME: New York City: January 26, 1991 Demonstration, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - NCPME: New York City: General, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - NCPME: New York City: General, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Cuba Information Project: Profesionales y Empresarios Cubanos Americanos (PECA), 1993 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Cuba Information Project: Promoting Enduring Peace, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Cuba Information Project: Queers for Cuba, Undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Cuba Information Project: UN Association of the USA, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Cuba Information Project: US-Cuba Trade and Economic Council, Undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Cuba Information Project: US Peace Council, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Cuba Information Project: Venceremos Brigade, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Cuba Information Project: Venceremos Brigade: Twenty-Fifth Anniversary, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Cuba Information Project: Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, 1990-1996 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Cuba Information Project: Chester King, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Cuba Information Project: Pastors for Peace, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Cuba Information Project: Antonio Maceo Brigade, 1993-1996 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Cuba Information Project: Marazul (Travel Agency), 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Cuba Information Project: Musicians United to Send Instruments to Cuba (MUSIC), 1995-1996. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Cuba Information Project: Nicaragua Solidarity Network, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Cuba Information Project: Office of the Americas, 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Cuba Information Project: Out Now, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Cuba Information Project: Time to Heal and Pastors for Peace, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Cuba Information Project: Other Organizations and Projects, 1990-1994 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Cuba Information Project: American Medical Students Association (Gainesville, Florida), 1994 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Cuba Information Project: Association for Free Trade with Cuba, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Cuba Information Project: Baptist Peace Fellowship, 1992-1995 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Cuba Information Project: First and Second International Trade Union Conferences in Solidarity with Cuba, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Cuba Information Project: Labor: General, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Cuba Information Project: US/Cuba Labor Exchange, 1991-1997 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Cuba Information Project: International Peace Appeal (Ramsey Clark, et al.), 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Cuba Information Project: International Youth Brigade to Cuba, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Cuba Information Project: Infomed, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Cuba Information Project: Interconnect, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Cuba Information Project: International Peace with Cuba Appeal (and Workers World), 1993-1996 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - US-Cuba Medical Project: "Project: Hearts and Minds" (Veterans for Peace), 1992 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - US-Cuba Medical Project: Medical Project: Legal, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - US-Cuba Medical Project: Irwin Corey Delegation, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - US-Cuba Medical Project: Sara Gonzalez (Contains Photographs), 1994 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - US-Cuba Medical Project: Contact with Cubans, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - US-Cuba Medical Project: Project Brochure, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - US-Cuba Medical Project: Meeting Minutes, 1991-1996 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - US-Cuba Medical Project: Outreach and Media, 1991-1994 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - US-Cuba Medical Project: Advisory Board, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - US-Cuba Medical Project: General, 1991-1996 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Cuba Information Project: National Network on Cuba: General, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Cuba Information Project: National Network on Cuba: United Nations Task Force: March 20, 1993 Miami Meeting, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Cuba Information Project: National Network on Cuba: Legislative Task Force, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Cuba Information Project: National Network on Cuba: General, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Cuba Information Project: Caribbean International Education Committee, North Carolina, 1992-1994 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cincinnati, Ohio, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cleveland, Ohio, 1991-1996 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Cuba Information Project: Poughkeepsie, NY (CLASP), 1996 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Cuba Information Project: US Health Care Trade Union Committee, Undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Cuba Information Project: Dominican Friends of Cuba, NYC, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Cuba Information Project: New York City, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Cuba Information Project: Twin Cities Cuba Network, Minneapolis, Minnesota, Undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Cuba Information Project: Columbia, Missouri, Undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Cuba Information Project: Committee for Cuba, Kansas City, Missouri, Undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Cuba Information Project: St. Louis, Missouri, Undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Cuba Information Project: Northeast Cuba Solidarity Network, 1993-1995 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Cuba Information Project: New Hampshire, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Cuba Information Project: Hermanas, New Jersey, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Cuba Information Project: New Jersey, 1993-1995 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cuban-American Committee, New Jersey, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Cuba Information Project: Jersey City, New Jersey, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Cuba Information Project: Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1991-1995 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Cuba Information Project: Rio Rancho, New Mexico, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Cuba Information Project: Upstate New York, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Cuba Information Project: Huntington, NY, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cubanos Contra El Bloqueo, NYC, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Cuba Information Project: Hands Off Cuba, NYC, 1990-1995 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Cuba Information Project: Cambridge, Boston, Massachusetts, 1991; undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Cuba Information Project: Maine, 1993-1996 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Cuba Information Project: Boston, Massachusetts, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Cuba Information Project: Pioneer Valley Coalition to Lift the Cuban Embargo, Western, Massachusetts, 1993-1995 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Cuba Information Project: Baltimore, Maryland, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Cuba Information Project: Columbia, Maryland, 1993-1995 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Cuba Information Project: Michigan, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Cuba Information Project: Food First, 1994-19960 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Cuba Information Project: Freedom Socialist Party, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Cuba Information Project: Fund for New Priorities, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 33)